Guide to the Church of Christ, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Church of Christ, Yale University, records
1757-1995
RU 512
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4
The records consist of minutes, sermons, a visitors register, and bulletins documenting the activities of the Church of Christ in Yale University. Also included are the records of Charles Krigbaum, university organist and choir director.
Yale College (1718-1887). Church of Christ
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 39-A (YRG 39-A), Records documenting official religious activities at Yale.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is partially restricted. See inventory for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes, sermons, a visitors register, and bulletins documenting the activities of the Church of Christ in Yale University. Also included are the records of Charles Krigbaum, university organist and choir director.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Church work; College students -- Religious life; Universities and colleges -- Religion; Sermons; Krigbaum, Charles; Yale College (1718-1887). Church of Christ; Yale University -- Religion; Yale University -- Students
- Records, 1792-1869; Accession 19ND-A-162
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Catalogue of Members, 1757-1927 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Church of Christ Records, 1757-1922 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
  - Committee of Church Deacons--minutes and records, 1837-1864 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Sermons preached in Battell Chapel, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Visitor"s Register, Dwight Hall, 1888-1925 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Church of Christ in Yale Bulletin, 1947-1981; Accession 2005-A-076
  - Church of Christ in Yale bulletin, 1947-1981 (Box 1)
- Records of Charles Krigbaum as University Organist and Choir Director, 1960-1995; Accession 2005-A-077
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2031
  - Records of Charles Krigbaum as university organist and choir director, 1960-1995 (Box 1)
  - Records of Charles Krigbaum as university organist and choir director, 1960-1995 (Box 2)
  - Records of Charles Krigbaum as university organist and choir director, 1960-1995 (Box 3)